diffeyewear.com 2017-06-06

# PRIVACY POLICY | DIFF Eyewear

**Privacy Policy**

DIFF Eyewear has created this privacy policy to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information submitted by you on diffeyewear.com. Please review it carefully.

**Information Collection**

DIFF Eyewear collects information to improve our site, services, overall customer experience, and for statistical measurements. The information you provide is stored in-house at DIFF Eyewear, and is used by us, and DIFF Eyewear partners. ****

> **Personal Information**
> 
> When you join our mailing list, create an account, or make a purchase through our site, your personal information is collected and stored. Basic personal information we collect includes, but is not limited to, your full name, billing address, shipping address, phone number, and email address.
> 
> When making a purchase through our site, our third party payment processor collects your credit card number, billing address, and name. These third party service providers are not authorized or permitted to use your personal information for any other reason than those pertaining to processing order transactions. We do not store credit card information after the transaction is complete.
> 
> We may also use your mailing address provided at checkout to send marketing and promotional items.
> 
> **Non-Identifying Information**
> 
> Non-identifying information are solo portions of your personal information that cannot be linked to you when seen alone, for example, your zip code or state. DIFF Eyewear uses non-identifying information for statistical measurements to ultimately improve your experience on our site. We may combine your non-identifying information with your personal information to provide services to you, such as delivering product or addressing your inquiries.

**Log Data**

When you visit diffeyewear.com, our servers will automatically record and store information that your browser sends to every website you visit. This information is called log data. Log data can include, but is not limited to, your Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser type, web address you were visiting before coming to diffeyewear.com, search information, the diffeyewear.com pages you visited and duration of time spent on each page. We collect this information to analyze and optimize our site to provide the utmost functionality to you.

**Cookies**

When visiting our site, DIFF Eyewear will place a “cookie” on your browsing system. A “cookie” is a piece of data that is sent to your browsing system to allow for an optimized experience on our site. Persistent and session cookies on your browser will allow us to remember your login information and cart items when you return to our site. Parts of these cookies will be deleted when you close your browser, or log out of your account on diffeyewear.com. We recommend allowing the use of cookies so we can provide the best online experience possible, however, if you wish to browse privately, without the use of cookies, you may instruct your browser to do so.

**E-Mails**

DIFF Eyewear collects your email address to provide necessary transaction confirmation notifications. You may also opt to be a part of our DIFF Eyewear mailing list. By doing so, we will use your email address to provide promotional or marketing material regarding the launch of new products, events, service, and other items of interest.

**Information Sharing**

The following includes a list of instances in which your personal information may be shared.

**             Data Security**

> Your DIFF Eyewear account information is password protected for your personal privacy and security. We ask that you take precautions to protect your personal information, for example using a password that contains a combination of numbers and letters, as well as frequently changing your password. Additionally, DIFF Eyewear uses a security socket layer (SSL) to encrypt sensitive information like your credit card number. While DIFF Eyewear utilizes electronic, and managerial procedures to protect this data against theft, or misuse, we cannot ensure the security of the information you transmit to us.

**             Service Providers**

> At times, DIFF Eyewear will employ third party service providers to assist us in improving our site. These services may include website maintenance, database management, website analytics, or payment processing parties. The service providers DIFF Eyewear employs will come in contact with your personal information, but are legally required to keep your information confidential under all circumstances.

**             Law Enforcement**

> If we deem it necessary or appropriate, DIFF Eyewear will cooperate with law enforcement officials and private parties when asked to disclose any information about you.

**             Business Transfer**

> In the event that DIFF Eyewear transfers ownership, we may share your personal information during a merger, acquisition, reorganization, sale of assets, or declaration of bankruptcy.

**             Your Account Information**

> You may edit, update, or delete parts or all of your personal information from your user account at any time. You may edit your account information by logging into your account, or if you wish to delete your account entirely, please contact us at [support@diffeyewear.com](mailto:sales@diffeyewear.com). Although your account can be deleted, an archived copy may remain on file for business records.

**             International Transfer**

> If you are an international customer, you should be aware that your personal information is transferred to the United States for processing at our headquarters in California. The security laws in the United States may differ from your home country, or governmental jurisdiction. Your consent to this Privacy Policy, and submission of your personal information during a transaction or otherwise, represents your agreement to that transfer.

**             Third-party links**

> diffeyewear.com or DIFF Eyewear’s email newsletters may contain links to third party websites. When you click on these links you will be transferred to the third party website. DIFF Eyewear does not exercise control over the third party’s privacy policy, and their privacy policy may differ from ours. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of the sites you visit.

**             Children**

> In compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act, DIFF Eyewear will not knowingly collect any information from children under the age of 13 years. If you are under 13, please have your parents or legal guardian enter their information when required. If a parent or legal guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided their personal information without parental consent, please contact [support@diffeyewear.com](mailto:support@diffeyewear.com "diff support email"), and we will remove the information from our files. Additionally, if DIFF Eyewear becomes aware that a child under the age of 13 has provided us with their personal information, we will delete the information from our files.

**Contact**

If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy, please contact DIFF Eyewear at support@diffeyewear.com or 15606 Broadway Center Street, Gardena CA, 90248.
